All right.
(カカシ)よし これより
我々は イタチ捜索及び➡
Starting now, our main mission
is to find Itachi
and take him into custody.
その捕獲を主とする任務に入る。
- Yeah!
- Yes!
(ナルト)おう！
(カカシ)暁の目的は尾獣集め。
Akatsuki's goal is to round up
the Tailed Beasts.
It is believed that they already
have the Three-Tails.
すでに 三尾も
手にしたものと思われる。
自来也様の情報によると
ターゲットのナルトを狙い➡
According to the data
obtained by Jiraiya-sama,
it's possible they have infiltrated
the Land of Fire and will target Naruto.
すでに 火ノ国に入ってきていても
おかしくない。
Itachi, in particular, is originally
from the Leaf Village.
特に イタチは木ノ葉の出身だ。
Three years ago, he returned to
the village
３年前にも ナルトを狙って
里に潜入したこともある。
and attempted to take Naruto.
So he's headed for
the Leaf Village again?
(サイ)今回も 木ノ葉に向かってると
考えられるってことですね。
As well as Sasuke-kun
who is after this Uchiha Itachi!
(サクラ)その うちはイタチを狙って
サスケ君も…。
Alright!
あぁ 必ず
サスケに たどり着いてみせる。
I'm gonna meet up
with Sasuke no matter what.
(ヤマト)まぁ そう欲張らず
一歩一歩いきましょう。
Well, let's just take it
one step at a time.
Here's the search plan.
(カカシ)捜索の手順を言う。
とりあえず ここを中心ポイントにして
近辺５キロ四方を探索する。
Using this as the central point,
we'll search all four directions
for five kilometers.
If we find nothing,
もし 何もなければ➡
then we'll move the central point and
spread out five kilometers from there.
中心ポイントを移動して
またそこから ５キロ四方を…。
And... we'll keep repeating this strategy.
ま… それを繰り返すわけだ。
Five kilometers...
Our wireless radio will be out of range!
５キロって…。
そんなに離れたら
無線も使えないじゃないですか！
And if we're separated,
it'll be dangerous!
それに 単独で
そこまで離れたら 危険です。
パトロールは 最低でも➡
The rules state that all patrols must
be done by two-man cells.
ツーマンセルが原則です。
敵に遭遇した場合…。
- If we encounter the enemy--!
- Sakura...
(ヤマト)サクラ そう焦らない。
(カカシ)まぁ 見てな。
Don't get so worried.
Just watch...
(パックン)拙者たちの声は
無線より遠くこだまし➡
Our voices which travel even farther
than the wireless radios,
and our noses that can instantly
sniff out danger, will protect you.
鼻で危険を
いち早く察知し 援護する。
Pakkun!
パックン！
All right, let me explain
the patrol team formation.
じゃあ パトロール隊の
チーム編成を説明する。
This time, two ninja hounds will
be assigned to each member.
今回は用心して
忍犬を１人に２匹つけるから。
Two dogs...? Huh? But...
２匹？ えっ でも…。
それじゃあ
仲よくしてあげてちょうだい。
Get along, all of you.
(シバ)よろしく サクラちゃん。
Hello, Sakura-chan.
You're such a snappy female
as usual.
(ビスケ)アンタ
口うるさいメスだな いつも。
I'm partnering with Shino.
(アキノ)オレは シノにつくワン。
(グルコ)ん… 虫くさいな。
Ugh... You stink of insects.
(シノ)犬くさい…。
You stink like a dog.
Hello.
よろしく。
(ウーヘイ)ひとつ 仲よくいこうぜ。
Let's work together...
In peace and harmony...
Hehehe!
(ウルシ)和気あいあいとな ヘヘヘ。
《犬と友達に… なれるかな？》
I wonder if...
I can become friends with dogs?
What about me?
じゃあ オレは？
Naruto, you're the Jinchuriki
they're targeting.
ナルトは人柱力で狙われている。
Just in case you're attacked,
襲われた場合のことを考えて➡
you'll be with Yamato and
Sensory-Scout Hinata.
ヤマトと 感知タイプのヒナタを同行させる。
And Big Bark Bull.
それに 大声のブルもだ。
(ブル)ワン！
L-Let's work together, Naruto-kun.
(ヒナタ)よ よろしくね ナルト君。
おう。
Right!
And being ninja-hound users,
Kiba and I will each have one dog.
で 忍犬使いのオレとキバは １匹ずつ。
So we're all set!
(キバ)これで 準備オッケーだぜ！
(カカシ)いいか みんな。
Listen up, everyone.
Above all, you will track
Itachi and Sasuke's scents.
とにかく イタチ サスケ
この２人のにおいを追う。
If you find either one of them,
そして
いずれかを見つけたとしても➡
verify their location,
then return to this spot.
場所を把握して
いったん このポイントまで戻ること。
Especially you, Naruto.
Don't go running off ahead of us.
特に ナルト 先走るなよ。
わかったってばよ。
I know.
All right then, let's head out.
じゃあ いきますか。
Scatter!
散！
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
the "impulses" that makes you want to meet it
aitaku naru no shoudou
the "innocence" that makes you want to cry
nakitaku naru no junjou
they've gone into the summer fire
natsu no hi ni tobikonda
the fireflies aren't coming back
hotaru wa kaeranai
you didn't say a single word and left a kiss for me behind
anata wa nanimo iwazu kuchizuke wo nokoshite
and nodded as you still got burned
kitsuzuku mama unazuita ne
it was so sad that my life was wavering
kanashii hodo inochi yurameiteita
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
sha la la my sweet lovely dear
sha la la itoshiki hito
I can also see you right now
anata mo mieteiru no
the dazzling moon will softly
mabayui tsuki ga sotto
illuminate the morning day
ashita wo terashite
and strongly and strongly shine on
tsuyoku tsuyoku kagayaite
The Hunt
(水月)じゃ 行ってくるよ。
I'm going.
Uchiha Itachi, eh?
I hope we can find him.
(重吾)うちはイタチか。
うまく見つかるといいが。
(香燐)よし！
All right!
Sa-su-ke!
サスケ～ ウチは～ サスケと２人で…。
I'm staying with you!
(サスケ)お前も さっさと行け。
You too. Get going.
チェッ！
Tch!
(デイダラ)もう問題ないな うん。
It's completely healed...
Yeah.
And? Which one are we going for?
(トビ)で どっちに行くんですか？
サスケか九尾か。
Sasuke or the Nine-Tails...?
さて どっちにしようかな…。
Well now, which will it be...?
あっ ちょっと あららら！
ちょ… ちょっと デイダラ先輩！
W-W-Wait, D-Deidara-senpai!
待ってくださいよ～！
Wait up!
PAWN SHOP
誰だ？ テメエは。
Who are you?!
下っ端ならいいか。
I guess underlings don't matter.
ちょっと様子見てこい。
はい。
Go and check.
Yes.
Huh? Who are you?!
誰だ テメエ？
You're that Akatsuki...
What's his name?
アンタ 暁の… 何て言ったっけな？
カク… カクタ。 カクサ… カクシ…。
Kaku... Kakuta... Kakusa... Kakushi...
か 角都。
K-Kakuzu...
Yes, that's the one.
そうそう。 アンタ その角都って
男の部下で帳簿係だよね？
You're that Kakuzu's henchman-
his bookkeeper, right?
な なんでも言う。
だ だから命だけは…。
I'll tell you anything
you want to know.
J-Just please don't kill me...
その調子で続けな。
That's the way... Keep talking.
キミらに聞くか。
Let me ask you guys...
赤丸 他の忍犬に負けるなよ。
Akamaru! Don't lose to
the other ninja hounds!
オレたちが最初にサスケの。
イタチのにおいを突き止めるんだ。
We'll be the first to detect Sasuke
and Itachi's scents!
(赤丸)ワン。
遅いぞ シノ。
モタモタするなワン。
You're too slow, Shino!
Don't dawdle!
虫が好かない。
I don't like them...
いくよ。 ポチ タマ。
Let's go! Pochi! Tama!
ポチって。
タマって。
Pochi...?
Tama?!
Don't give me silly nicknames!
勝手にあだ名つけんでくれるかな。
Sasuke...
《サスケ》
If you don't wipe that solemn look
off your face,
そんな思いつめた顔でいたら
男は逃げるばかりだぜ。
you'll scare off the boys.
What?
なによ。
追えば追うほど オスは逃げる。
The more you chase,
the further they run away.
アンタ 押しっぱなしのメスだったろ。
押してダメなら引いてみな。
You're a female that keeps
on pushing, aren't you?
Why don't you try pulling away
for a change?
変なこと言わないでよ。
What a thing to say!
私とサスケ君は
そんなんじゃないんだから。
Sasuke-kun and I...
aren't like that...
Hey, stop being so rude.
コラ お前さん口が悪いぞ。
フン。
Humph!
ただ私は サスケ君に 私の…
みんなの言葉を伝えたいだけ。
It's just that I want to
let Sasuke know...
how I... how everyone feels.
Everyone is waiting for Sasuke
to return home.
みんな サスケ君が帰ってくるのを
待ってるって。 ただ それだけ。
That's all...
わかったよ。
じゃあ引いてダメなら吸ってみよう。
Fine. Well, if pulling away doesn't work,
why don't I try sniffing?
What's the matter?!
どうしたの？
かすかだが
うちはサスケのにおいがする。
I caught a whiff of
Uchiha Sasuke's scent...
なんですって？
What?!
Well?
どう？
においがはっきりしない。
The smell is faint,
but it's steadily getting closer.
だが どんどん近づいてくる。
What are you doing?!
He'll be on to us before we find him!
なにやってる。
こちらが見つける前に
見つかっちまうぜ。
We have to be cautious!
慎重にいくぞ。
He's near.
近いぞ。
Sakura-chan, do you see Sasuke around?
サクラちゃん。
近くにいないか サスケが？
ダメだ。 においが離れていく。
This isn't good.
The smell is going farther away.
《ひと回りしたけど
これといったチャクラも感じなかった。
I've given it a once-over,
but I don't sense any chakra.
戻っちゃおうかな サスケのとこ。
Maybe I'll go back to Sasuke.
The other two are probably
not back yet.
あの２人は
まだ帰ってないだろうし》
I found it, Tobi!
見つけたぞ トビ… うん。
Yeah!
No kidding?! That was fast!
マジっすか!? 速っ！
And? Which one is it?
The Nine-Tails or Sasuke?
で どっちっすか？ 九尾かサスケか。
こりゃ都合がいい。
２人でいくぞ トビ。
What an opportunity.
We're going together, Tobi.
So... Which one?
だから どっち？
フッ… ついてこい！
Just follow me!
Yes.
(トビ)はい。
ナルト ヒナタ… わかってるね？
Naruto... Hinata...
You understand, right?
Yes.
はい。
あぁ。
Yeah...
You're...!
お前は…。
出てこい。 何者だ？
Show yourself...
Who are you?
(カブト)やっぱり バレましたか。
You found me, after all...
Yakushi Kabuto...
薬師カブト…。
You've got guts approaching us
by yourself.
自分から近づいてくるとは
いい度胸だな。
ナルト君と少し話がしたくてね。
I wanted to have a chat
with Naruto.
You're not getting away this time.
We're taking you in.
今度は逃がさない。
お前を拘束する。
Hey! Kabuto! You would know!
Where is Sasuke?!
おいカブト！ お前なら知ってんだろ。
サスケは どこにいる？
フッ… 相変わらず サスケ サスケかい？
Humph! Still can't get over Sasuke, eh...?
サスケが大蛇丸をやったっていうのは
本当なのか？
Is it true that Sasuke
killed Orochimaru?!
あぁ 本当だよ。
Yeah... It's true.
More importantly,
I brought you a present today.
そんなことより 今日は
ナルト君にプレゼントを持ってきたんだよ。
That outfit... You're...
その装束… お前は？
キミがサスケ君かぁ。
So you're Sasuke-kun...
You really do look like Itachi-san!
やっぱり似てるわ イタチさんと。
S-Scary!
怖っ！
Release!
《喝！》
ヘッ！
What's that?
何だ それは？
Information our organization
has gathered regarding Akatsuki.
かつて ボクたちの組織が集めてた
暁に関する情報だよ。
What of it?
何で そんなもん…。
It's yours. You can have it.
あげるよ キミたちに。
大蛇丸なき今➡
Now that Orochimaru is dead...
you're trying to negotiate with us?
それで 木ノ葉と
取り引きしようとでもいうのか？
(カブト)いや… こんなもので
取り引きできるほど➡
Nope... I don't think it's as easy
as negotiating with something like this...
甘くないでしょ 木ノ葉は特に。
Especially with the Leaf Village.
Then why?
なら何だ？
お前は大蛇丸と違って➡
Unlike Orochimaru,
Akatsuki isn't after you.
暁に追われてるわけでも
ないんだろ？
ナルト君に感謝を込めて。
ただのプレゼントさ。
It's a simple gift to Naruto-kun.
A token of my gratitude.
Plus, Akatsuki is pursuing you.
キミは暁に狙われてるしね。
Gratitude...?
感謝？
After Orochimaru-sama died,
ボクは 大蛇丸様が死んでから➡
I lost sense of who I was.
自分が何者か
また わからなくなった。
親も知らず 国も知らず➡
I never knew my parents
or my homeland.
The enemy found me and
from the time I was little,
敵に拾われ
幼い頃からスパイとして➡
I moved around the lands
and villages as a spy.
国や里を転々としていた
ボクにとって➡
国や里といったものは
曖昧なものでしかなかった。
Lands and villages didn't
mean much to me.
That is, until I began serving
Orochimaru-sama...
大蛇丸様の部下になるまではね…。
だが また なくなってしまった。
But now, he's gone too.
Just who am I?
The agony of not having an identity...
自分は いったい何者なのか…。
アイデンティティーのない この苦しみ➡
You can understand,
can't you, Naruto?
キミなら
わかってくれるよね ナルト君。
お前の言うことなんか わかるか！
Like I'd understand
anything you say!
フッ… そうかな。
Humph... I wonder about that.
自分は うずまきナルトなのか
それとも九尾なのか…。
Are you Uzumaki Naruto?
Or are you the Nine-Tails?
In the past, you were shunned...
regarded with loathing.
かつてキミは
他人の冷たい視線にさらされ➡
You must have questioned yourself
about who you really are.
いったい自分が何なのか
わからなくなってたはずだ。
しかし キミは自分の力を信じ➡
However, you had faith
in your strength
and told yourself that
you were Naruto Uzumaki...
自分は うずまきナルトなんだと➡
and you boldly overcame
their views about the Nine-Tails.
九尾に対する視線を
力強く乗り越えてきた。
あの人は ナルト君を
どうしようと…。
What does he intend...
to do with Naruto-kun?
I can't figure out his intentions...
ヤツの出方が見えない。
だからキミは 自分のアイデンティティーも
よく知ってるし➡
And that's why you are sure
of your identity
キミを認めてくれる仲間も出来た。
and you found friends
who accept you.
But instead of overcoming
Orochimaru-sama,
だがボクは
大蛇丸様を超えようとせず➡
I desperately clung to his power.
ただ
その力にすがりついてただけだ。
I'm really able to understand
how you feel now.
今ならキミの気持が本当にわかるよ。
ボクは キミに気づかされた。
You made me realize...
that I want to be like you.
ボクもキミのようになりたいと思えた。
だから今度は…。
So now...
I'm going to surpass Orochimaru-sama
who I absorbed,
この体に取り込んだ
大蛇丸様を超え➡
and discover a new, stronger self.
新たな強い自分を見つけるよ。
I'll find my new self...
新たな自分を見つける…
キミは そのヒントをくれた。
and you have given me
a hint to finding it.
That's why I'm grateful... Naruto-kun.
だから感謝してるのさ… ナルト君。
大蛇丸様は再生の象徴。
Orochimaru-sama is
the symbol of reincarnation.
He continues to live on inside me,
as an existence that I must overcome.
ボクの超えるべき存在として
ボクの中で生き続ける。
取り込んだだと!?
なに…。
Took... into your body?
Well...
It was just a small segment
of Orochimaru-sama's corpse
サスケ君が倒した
大蛇丸様の亡骸の一部を➡
after Sasuke-kun killed him...
which I transplanted into my own body.
少しばかり
この体に移植しただけさ。
とはいえ
すさまじいほどの生命力だよ。
But, his life-force is amazing.
It's now steadily trying to
take over my body... this thing.
逆にボクの体をどんどん
取り込もうとするんだ。 これがね。
バカなことを…。
That's ridiculous...
What is that?
《何？ あれ…。
Byakugan!
白眼!!
もう 体の３割は取り込まれてる》
One-third of his body has
already been taken over.
取り込まれまいと
必死に抵抗する自分がいる。
But I've been fiercely resisting
this takeover!
大蛇丸様を超えようとしている
自分の存在を実感できる！
I can feel this part of me that's trying
to overcome Orochimaru-sama!
Is that all you want to say?
言いたいことは それだけかよ。
へっ。
せいぜい がんばれってばよ！
木ノ葉の檻の中でな!!
Well, give it everything you've got!
In a jail cell in Leaf Village!
木遁！
Wood Style!
All right! Gotcha!
よっしゃ！ 捕まえた!!
Behind you!
後ろ！
ハハハハ！
クッソ！
Dammit...
この大蛇丸様の力を完全に
コントロールできるようになったら➡
When I'm able to fully control
Orochimaru-sama's power,
I will fight you again, Naruto-kun.
ちゃんと戦ってあげるよ ナルト君。
But you come later.
でも キミは あとだ。
First, it'll be Sasuke-kun who
brought down Orochimaru-sama.
まずは 大蛇丸様を倒した
サスケ君が優先だ。
What're you gonna do to Sasuke?!
お前 サスケをどうしようと!?
また会おう。
Until we meet again.
やったぜ！ サスケを倒したぜ うん。
We did it!
We brought down Sasuke.
As expected, Senpai...
さすが先輩！
さすが先輩。
うるせえ！
As expected, Senpai.
Shut up!
でも
少しはやるようっすね この人。
But looks like he's kinda strong...
this guy.
ケッ！ こんなガキに
あの大蛇丸がやられたとはな。
Imagine Orochimaru being killed
by a brat like him.
I still can't believe it...
いまだに信じられねえぜ うん。
Huh?
いい目で
にらみやがってるぜ トビ！ うん！
Tobi, look how
he's glaring at us! Humph!
You're raring to go, eh Senpai?
張り切っちゃってるなぁ 先輩。
イタチさんに あとで謝らなきゃ。
You'll have to apologize to Itachi-san later.
keep your pants and shirt on even if you're unable to do it right now
ima dekinakute mo aseranaide awatenaide
you should believe in yourself and take it at your own pace
kimi no mai peesu de jibun shinjite yukkuri ikeba ii
life always throws you curveballs and the reason of that is
yo kono yo wa hitosujinawa de ikanai sore wa naze nara
it's a test made by God so that's why it's quite hard
kamisama ga tsukutta tesuto dakara muzukashii nda
arts? science? or rather how about ethics?
bunkei rikei mushiro doutoku kimi nara kore wo dou toku
this is just like life so put your heart and soul into seriousness
kore wa maru de jinsei dakara uchikomu shinken ni
we worry ourselves lose ourselves and we keep asking ourselves questions
bokura wa nayamu mayou nandomo jibun ni toikakeru
we aren't one and relentesly persue our search for answers
hitotsu ja nai kotae sagashi gamushara ni oikakeru
keep your pants and shirt on even if you're unable to do it right now
ima dekinakute mo aseranaide awatenaide
you should believe in yourself and take it at your own pace
kimi no mai peesu de jibun shinjite yukkuri ikeba ii
the current me would tell me that if I was from the future
mirai no bokura nara ima no boku ni oshiete agerareru
you should keep pursuing it until your efforts change yourself
kimi no doryoku ga jishin ni kawaru toki made oitsuzukereba ii
Next Episode
You guys must be Akatsuki.
Where's Uchiha Itachi?
Huh?
(ハデス)思いがけず 古なじみと➡
If you tell me nicely,
I'll let you go.
再会する羽目になったものよ。
What shall we do, Senpai?
He's playing hardball.
Sharingan... eh?
You're Itachi's younger brother, all right.
だが フェアリーテイルを壊滅させるのは➡
本来の目的のついでにすぎん。
So you were able to kill Orochimaru
because of your Uchiha bloodline...
我らの狙いは
伝説の黒魔導士 ゼレフ。
Lucky enough to be born into that family!
That's all it was!
If you don't feel like telling me,
that's fine.
七眷属よ
よい報告を待っておるぞ。
I'll just wring the information
from you by force.
Clash!
Next time: "Clash!"
"Pawn Shop"
Oh...
Once again, the due date for
Tsunade-sama's debt is looming.
Tonton! We have no choice.
Let's go and do that thing
like we used to!
Huh?
You'll catch a cold sleeping out here.
Oww...
Are you all right, Aniki...?
Um...
I'd like to borrow some money.
Aniki! This one's a winner!
I know! I know!
If we sell her,
I think we'll get over a million ryo!
All right! How about 500,000 ryo?
Thank you very much!
I'm sorry!
Aniki, the pig disappeared!
What?! What a day
this is turning out to be!